<tips>
<me1>
  <tip>Since the Prothean extinction, numerous species have come to call the Citadel home.&#x0a;It serves as the political, cultural, and financial capital of the galactic community.</tip>
  <tip>Terra Nova was one of the Class-1 colonization prospects discovered by the first wave&#x0a;of Alliance surveys in 2150. It currently has the highest population of any Alliance colony.</tip>
  <tip>The First Contact War, referred to as the Relay 314 Incident by the turians,&#x0a;was a small, three-month conflict between the human Systems Alliance and the Turian Hierarchy.</tip>
  <tip>A race of four-eyed bipeds native to the world of Khar'shan, the batarians are a&#x0a;disreputable species that chose to isolate itself from the rest of the galaxy.</tip>
  <tip>Omni-tools are multipurpose diagnostic and manufacturing tools as well as computers used&#x0a;for a variety of civilian and battlefield tasks, such as hacking, decryption, or repair.</tip>
  <tip>The second species to join the Citadel, the salarians are warm-blooded amphibians&#x0a;native to the planet Sur'Kesh.</tip>
  <tip>The asari, native to the planet Thessia, are often considered the most influential&#x0a; species in the galaxy, and are known for their elegance, and biotic aptitude.</tip>
  <tip>The krogan are a species of large reptilian bipeds native to the planet Tuchanka, a world&#x0a;known for its harsh environments, scarce resources, and overabundance of vicious predators.</tip>
  <tip>Noveria is a small, frozen terrestrial world, barely habitable by conventional definitions.&#x0a;The planet is often used to perform research too dangerous or controversial to be performed elsewhere.</tip>
  <tip>The ExoGeni Corporation has founded a pilot colony on Feros to explore the Prothean&#x0a;ruins that blanket two-thirds of the planet's land mass. The atmosphere is fouled with dust.</tip>
  <tip>The five arms of the Citadel are known as the Wards. They are the residential&#x0a;centers of the Citadel, each essentially a self-contained city home to millions.</tip>
  <tip>Omni-gel is a technological material designed for use with omni-tools&#x0a;to do electronics or decryption work.</tip>
  <tip>Medi-gel is an all-purpose medicinal salve combining an anaesthetic and clotting&#x0a;agent used by paramedics, EMTs, and military personnel, produced by the Sirta Foundation.</tip>
  <tip>Mass Relays are mass transit devices scattered throughout the Milky Way, usually located&#x0a;within star systems. They form an enormous network allowing interstellar travel.</tip>
  <tip>Kills while in the Mako grant much less XP than kills on foot.</tip>
  <tip>Citadel Security Services, or C-Sec, handles law enforcementon the Citadel.&#x0a;It is a volunteer police service answering to the Citadel Council.</tip>
</me1>
<me2>
  <tip>Due to their widespread network, Cerberus effectively has access to almost every&#x0a;settled system,major trade stop, and colony in the galaxy.</tip>
  <tip>The M-44 Hammerhead is an infantry fighting vehicle that hovers over the&#x0a;battlefieldat up to 120 kilometers an hour.</tip>
  <tip>The Ismar Frontier is an Attican Traverse cluster at the galactic rim,&#x0a;near the bordersof Outer Council Space.</tip>
  <tip>Drell are omnivorous reptile-like humanoids with an average lifespan of 85 galactic standard years.</tip>
  <tip>Many vorcha are trained by the krogan Blood Pack as mercenaries due to their savage nature&#x0a;and adaptability to different environments.</tip>
  <tip>Around 1900 BCE, the krogan discovered atomic power and promptly instigated many intraplanetary wars,&#x0a;sending Tuchanka into a nuclear winter.</tip>
  <tip>Heavy pistols are a class of semi-automatic weapons, which have a fairly low rate of fire&#x0a;and limited ammunition, but do relatively high damage per shot.</tip>
  <tip>To eliminate inefficiency, guns adopted detachable heat sinks known as thermal clips.</tip>
  <tip>Eezo is generated when solid matter, such as a planet, is affected by the energy of a star going supernova.&#x0a;The material is common in the asteroid debris that orbits neutron stars and pulsars.</tip>
  <tip>Medi-gel is an all-purpose medicinal salve combining an anaesthetic and clotting agent&#x0a;used by paramedics, EMTs, and military personnel, produced by the Sirta Foundation.</tip>
  <tip>The Citadel Fleet consists of a mixed group of turian, salarian, and asari vessels,&#x0a;though the greater number of them are turian.</tip>
  <tip>The shielding afforded by kinetic barriers does not protect against extremes of,&#x0a;temperature, toxins, or radiation.</tip>
  <tip>Starships still require conventional thrusters in addition to the FTL drive core.&#x0a;With only a core, a ship has no motive power.</tip>
  <tip>A starship's General Area Defense Integration Anti-spacecraft Network (GARDIAN) consists&#x0a;of anti-missile and anti-fighter laser turrets on the exterior hull.</tip>
  <tip>On their first three interstellar colonies, the salarians planted settlements named&#x0a;Aegohr, Mannovai, and Jaëto.</tip>
  <tip>Spectres (Special Tactics and Reconnaissance) are agents entrusted with extraordinary&#x0a;authority by the Citadel Council, including the power of life and death over the inhabitants of the galaxy.</tip>
  <tip>Originally a small Terminus Systems vorcha gang, the Blood Pack was transformed&#x0a;into a mercenary legion by visionary krogan battlemaster Ganar Wrang.</tip>
  <tip>Eclipse is a mercenary corporation that was founded by asari commando Jona Sederis.&#x0a;The organization provides effective security and firepower for prospective employers.</tip>
  <tip>The Blue Suns are a "private security organization",&#x0a;in reality a mercenary outfit, operating in the Skyllian Verge.</tip>
  <tip>The keepers are a mysterious, bio-engineered insectoid race that are native only&#x0a;to the Citadel. They are found throughout the Citadel in random locations, and are harmless.</tip>
</me2>
<me3>
  <tip>Without Salarian intervention, the effects of nuclear war on Tuchanka&#x0a;would have resulted in a slow but certain mass extinction.</tip>
  <tip>The Illusive Man is the elusive, secretive, and well informed leader of Cerberus.&#x0a;He has close-cropped silver-grey hair with "steely blue" eyes which appear to be prosthetic.</tip>
  <tip>N7 is a vocational code in the Systems Alliance military. The "N" designates&#x0a;special forces and the "7" refers to the highest level of proficiency.</tip>
  <tip>Barla Von is a volus financial adviser who runs an office in the Financial District of&#x0a;the Presidium. He is known for being able to move large sums of money without leaving a paper trail.</tip>
  <tip>Benning, the nearest garden world to Arcturus Station, is the primary source of its&#x0a;food supply and an important staging area for starship maintenance and repair.</tip>
  <tip>Supposedly constructed by the long-extinct Protheans,&#x0a;the Citadel serves as the capital of the Citadel Council.</tip>
  <tip>The elcor homeworld Dekuuna overflows with natural resources protected by law, from large&#x0a;deposits of precious metals to vast forests. The elcor themselves live in rich grasslands near the equator.</tip>
  <tip>Huerta Memorial Hospital is located on the Presidium of the Citadel. The hospital is&#x0a;named after President Christopher Huerta of the United North American States on Earth.</tip>
  <tip>Also known as the Flotilla, the Migrant Fleet is the massive collection of starships&#x0a;that became home to the quarians after they were driven from their home world by the geth.</tip>
  <tip>The hanar are a species resembling Earth's jellyfish and are one of the few non-bipedal&#x0a;Citadel races. Hanar are known for their intense politeness when speaking, and their strong religious beliefs.</tip>
  <tip>Cerberus arose from the tumult of the First Contact War in 2157 CE, a conflict between&#x0a;humanity and the first alien race they had encountered after achieving spaceflight, the turians.</tip>
  <tip>Duct Rats are poor, homeless children of the Citadel who travel in the ventilation system of the station.</tip>
</me3>
</tips>